Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Returning Pearl)
How does it taste?
You cook well, Lord Jing.
You seasoned the filling well.
Of course.
This is my mother's secret recipe.
Since I was ten years old,
I started acting and doing commercials.
From one unit to another
and acting from one role to another.
Real
and stable things
are few in my life.
So, when I was sad,
I'd make myself a bowl of wantons.
When I have this familiar taste,
my hear won't feel as empty.
That's good.
I no longer remember
the taste of my mother's cooking.
Sorry.
If I knew, I would've changed your back story
instead of making you suffer in such loneliness.
Sui Sui.
Were you lonely
in your world?
(Episode 28)
My parents
passed away one after another
a few years ago.
The environment I lived in
was a place of fame and fortune.
There were too many temptations, deceptions,
and far too many conflicts of interest.
I could only wear a mask
and put on a facade
to prevent myself from getting harmed.
I've always felt
that it's not true.
However, in this fairytale world,
I felt all of your sincerity
and loyalty.
Jing Yuan,
do you know?
No one has given me
warmth and love like you.
Me too.
I don't know
which world is real.
Sui Sui.
Although I don't understand your world,
I remember
how my mother insisted on choosing
to be with the person she loved
despite her family's objection.
They didn't spend the rest of their lives together
but I believe
she must be very happy
when she was in love with my father.
So, it's also the same
to me.
You exist.
Our love also exists.
Am I right, Sui Sui?
Yes.
So, I think
when your people created this story,
they were also trying to teach people
how to make a choice
between authority and true love.
You are right.
The story of "My Fair Princess"
was popular around the world back then.
Many people were touched by this story
because it talked about how precious
true love was.
Her Majesty used to tell me
that my mother was wrong.
After hearing that for a long time, I thought the same, too.
However, I felt a little unwilling to accept it.
You celebrated my birthday a few days ago
and asked me to make a wish.
Although you said a wish shouldn't be revealed to others,
I still want to tell you my wish.
The wish I made was
hoping that my birth wasn't a mistake.
Thank you.
My wish has come true.
Jing Yuan, sorry.
You will soon
return to your world.
No matter what,
I want to tell you
that you must pursue the most sincere love
regardless of your environment.
All right.
When I leave,
what do you plan to do?
I am
the director of the Department of Punishments.
I am someone with power and authority.
I will live a lavish life.
Perhaps I will get married and have children.
I'll be blessed with many descendants.
I don't need you to miss me.
But you are my male lead.
Besides me,
you won't have another romantic storyline.
That's even better.
I will focus on building my career.
The ambitions of a good man lie everywhere.
You must trust me.
I won't be tied down forever
by love.
Life is full of partings, reunions, joys, and sorrows.
It's something no one has ever been able to escape.
I'll think of you
as going to a faraway place.
When I miss you,
I will eat a bowl of wantons.
Perhaps you will also
be eating the same thing in that world
when you miss me.
Jing Yuan,
from now on,
no matter how far we are apart,
I will never forget you.
Sure.
By Heaven's will and the Emperor's decree,
Zi Wei is the emperor's biological daughter.
She was lost since she was young
and has finally been reunited.
It's the blessing of Heaven.
His Majesty will grant Zi Wei the title of Princess Ming Zhu
to prove her identity.
The commoner, Xiao Yan Zi,
will maintain her title of Princess Huan Zhu.
Both princesses will live in Shufang Hall
and enjoy His Majesty's grace.
End of decree.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Your Highnesses.
I'll be leaving.
Zi Wei.
- This is great. - Is this true?
I... I am still Princess Huan Zhu.
You are Princess Ming Zhu.
Lin Er, did you know this already?
Zi Wei is Princess Ming Zhu and I am still Princess Huan Zhu.
Heaven's secret cannot be revealed.
I'm so happy!
Tonight, we'll have a barbecue party at Shufang Hall!
Great!
Xiao Zhuo Zi, Xiao Deng Zi, Ming Yue, and Cai Xia.
Go and get prepared.
Prepare more meat.
All right. I'll go right away.
(The story of "My Fair Princess" has been completed.)
(Lin will return to the real world at the hour of Zi three days later.)
Sui Sui.
Three days later.
At the hour of Zi.
Three days later?
Three days later.
Lin Er.
- At the hour of Zi. - Lin Er.
What's wrong?
Three days later, at the hour of Zi,
I will be leaving.
Three days later?
- Yes. - Why must you leave so soon?
No. I'm reluctant to see you go, Lin Er.
Me too, Xiao Yan Zi.
I don't want you to leave.
- Zi Wei. - Lin Er.
I will miss all of you.
Everyone actually...
Doesn't need to be too worried.
Lin Er isn't leaving.
She's just going home.
She should return to her own world.
Right?
Isn't this a good thing?
All of us should feel happy.
Jing Yuan is right.
There's a time
for gathering and separating.
It has been this way since ancient times.
We shouldn't be upset about this.
Don't we still have three days?
Let's think of something fun to give Lin Er as a farewell.
That's right. Xiao Yan Zi, think of something.
Is there anything fun and delicious?
All right.
We will drink and eat to our heart's content.
We must send Lin Er home happily.
Don't cry.
- All right. - Promise me, all right?
Don't cry, okay?
Don't cry.
- Okay. - Okay.
All right.
Don't be sad and don't cry.
- Jing Yuan. - Yes?
I have a gift for you.
What gift?
I'm returning it to its rightful owner.
I hope
your life
will be smooth forever.
All right.
Yong Qi,
you can even draw?
Make me look prettier in your painting.
I want to look as pretty as Lin Er and Zi Wei.
Fifth Prince learns from Giuseppe Castiglione.
He draws like a master painter.
Look at this composition.
Jing Yuan might not be here
but Fifth Prince drew all of us in here.
Yes. I planned this for a long time.
Jing Yuan is busy working but he mustn't be left out.
When I finish this painting,
it'll be hung at Shufang Hall.
Even if she isn't around,
she will still be with everyone.
I, Lin Sui Sui, am unworthy
of this miraculous encounter
to be friends with all of you
and live a carefree life.
I will never forget all of you.